本字幕由YYeTs字幕组原创翻译
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    ustvboom
了解最新影视字幕发布信息
饥饿
的青春
第二季  第八集
《绝命毒师》第五季下载完毕
Breaking Bad season five downloaded.
今晚我们要看老白咯
Walter White is on tonight.
索菲亚  周五晚上了
Sofia, it's Friday night!
是的
Yeah, it is!
太阳出来我们才睡觉
We're not gonna sleep till the sun comes up!
那是必须的
You're damn right we're not!
你不换衣服吗
Aren't you gonna change?
我为什么要换衣服
Why would I change?
我们今晚要去泡吧
We're going out clubbing tonight.
不  我们今晚要看完《绝命毒师》
No, we're not. We're finishing breaking bad tonight.
你知道还有什么也"绝"了吗  你的约会生活
You know what's breaking bad? Your dating life.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我约会啊
I date.
你过去一年里才约了三次会
You've been on three dates in the past year
还找了个理由讨厌他们所有人
and you found a reason to hate all of them.
不是那样的
That's not true!
你记得超棒先生吗
You remember Mr. Brilliant?
我怎么能忘
How could I forget?
"交通超棒"
"The traffic is brilliant.
"灯光超棒"
"The lighting was brilliant.
"这些冰块超棒"
"These ice cubes are brilliant."
你也不喜欢瑞克
Okay, well, then you didn't like Rick
因为他给i上加点时画的是气泡
because he dotted his I's with a bubble.
他还用翻盖手机
And he had a flip phone.
我们是野人吗
What are we, cavemen?
听着
Okay, listen...
亲爱的  你想过也许你太挑剔了吗
Sweetie, did you ever think maybe you're just a little too picky?
不
No!
你只是不懂
Look, you just don't get it,
因为你有超级库珀熊
because you have a super Cooper bear.
是啊  所以我才一直催促你
Yeah, and that's why I'm pushing you so hard.
我也希望你拥有超棒的其他熊熊
I want you to have a super significant other bear.
不可能的
Well, it ain't gonna happen,
因为所有完美男人都有主了
because all the perfect guys are taken.
我遇到了完美的男人
I met the perfect guy!
马可
Marco!
波罗[水球]
Polo!
你在哪里遇见他的  游泳池吗
Where'd you meet him? The pool?
在"你好丘比特"的一池帅哥中遇见的
In the pool of hotties on "Heycupid."
那是一款约会应用
It's a dating app
你可以拿起手机
where you hold your phone up
如果附近有人喜欢你的资料...
and if a guy nearby likes your profile...
现在我有了马可
Now I have Marco.
他是个炫酷型男  开了一家精品肉店
He's cool, sexy, and owns a gourmet butcher shop.
索菲亚很久没吃到"好肉"了
Sofia hasn't had a good piece of meat in a while.
我们今晚要进行第二次约会了
So, uh, we're going on our second date tonight,
我过来拿点酒
so I just came to pick up some wine.
还有你们烤箱里的任何东西
And whatever might be in your oven.
妹子  我真高兴搬到了你们隔壁
Girl, I am so glad I moved next door.
-索菲亚  -别说
- Sofia-- - Don't even say it.
我不会用那款应用
I'm not using that app.
世界上的男人们  你们有过机会
Men of the world, you've had your chance.
老娘不陪你们玩了
My ass might not quit, but I do.
幸亏我不会
Yeah, well, luckily I don't.
"你好丘比特"  见见索菲亚·玛利亚·康斯薇拉·
"Heycupid," Meet Sofia Maria Consuelo
拉斐尔·罗德里格斯吧
Rafeala Rodriguez.
这会是自动纠错的噩梦
That's gonna be an autocorrect nightmare.
翻译  冰蓝   aaaBao   roaddog
校对  roaddog
时间轴  aaaBao
后期  斯人   总监  roaddog
我需要你停止可悲的生活
I need you to press pause on your pathetic little life
帮我藏起来乔什的东西
and help me hide Josh's stuff.
卡洛琳刚宣布订婚了
Caroline just announced her engagement.
什么
What?
但是她跟乔什两个月前才分手
But she and Josh broke up, like, two months ago.
我还以为她忙着
I thought she'd be too busy
用斑点狗皮做外套
making coats out of dalmatian puppies
来再次结婚呢
to get married again.
等等  乔什知道吗
Wait, does Josh know?
你觉得我为啥要藏起他的笔记本
Why do you think I'm hiding his laptop
智能手机
his smartphone...
还有这个震动的玩意儿
and whatever this vibrating thing is?
尤兰达刚告诉我卡洛琳订婚了吗
Yolanda just told me Caroline's engaged?
该死
Damn it!
听着  乔什
Listen, Josh,
卡洛琳订婚了
just because Caroline is engaged
并不意味着你应该垂头丧气
doesn't mean you need to go start feeling all bad about yourself.
我没啊
I don't.
比如说  我不够有魅力吗
You know, like, "Am I not charming enough?
-我不够幽默吗  我是不是胖了  -加比
- "Am I not funny enough? Am I getting fat?" - Gabi.
告诉你一下  乔什
Just for the record, Josh,
就算你肥了  我也依然爱你
I'd love you even if you did get fat.
各位  我为卡洛琳感到高兴
Guys, I'm happy for Caroline.
我们不是天生一对  没事的
We weren't meant to be together. It's all good.
你没必要为了我们逞英雄  大个儿
You don't need to be brave for us, big guy.
来吧
Bring it in.
我不用抱抱
I don't need to go in.
我没事
I'm good.
-我能告诉你一个秘密吗  -什么
- Can I tell you a secret? - What?
如果他胖了  我不会爱他
If he got fat, wouldn love him.
艾略特  你能帮我拿一下手机吗
Oh, Elliot, can you grab my phone?
我在忙着做饺子
I'm elbow-deep in dumplings.
我在忙着"我不在乎"
I'm elbow-deep in "I don't care."
拜托  我给索菲亚编了假约会档案
Please, I made Sofia a fake dating profile
每次它叮的一声  就说明她有了对象
and everytime it dings, it means she got a match.
你不想看看吗
Don't you want to see?
那男人没穿上衣吗
Are the guys shirtless?
-穿了  -那就不要
- No. - Then no.
该死
Shoot.
鲁本
Ooh, Ruben.
来看看  大学毕业生
Let's see, college graduate.
做营销
Works in marketing,
1米
five foot...
Eleven!
艾略特  看来我们有对象了
Elliot, it looks like we have a match.
你知道从统计学角度而言
Did you know, statistically,
手机比马桶还要脏吗
cellphones are dirtier than toilet seats?
不知道  失陪了  我要去卫生间
I did not. Excuse me, I'll be in the bathroom,
把脸擦烂为止
scrubbing my face till I bleed.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
马可要带我去吃午餐
Marco's taking me to lunch,
我打算扮嫩
and I'm trying to look young.
他要在20年前接你吗
Is he picking you up 20 years ago?
我要去补妆
I'm gonna go touch-up my makeup.
乔什的滚漆筒在洗衣间
Josh's paint roller is in the laundry room.
你好  我是来...
Hi, I'm here to--
艾略特
Elliot?
马可
Marco?
你就是跟尤兰达约会的马可吗
You're the Marco that's going out with Yolanda?
但你以前跟男人约会
But you used to date men,
我说的男人  是指我
and by men, I mean me.
好吧  这有点尴尬了
Okay, this just got a little weird.
麦当娜演唱会后我就没见过你
I haven't seen you since the Madonna concert.
你不该在那里甩了我
That was a terrible place to dump me.
之后我再也听不下去她的歌了
I haven't been able to listen to her music since.
亲爱的  没人能听
Honey, no one has.
艾略特
Oh, Elliot,
看来你已经见过马可了
I see you've already met Marco.
是的  我们刚见
Yes, we just met.
刚见
Just now.
不是在布拉德的托尼奖派对上认识的
Not at Brad's Tony Awards party.
走吧  宝贝
Well, let's go, baby.
马可  你真的不觉得"走后门"
Marco, are you sure you wouldn't be more comfortable
更舒服吗
using the back door?
我们午饭吃什么呢  宝贝
So... what are we thinking for lunch, babe?
泰国菜  意大利菜
Thai? Italian?
为什么不尝尝韩国菜[韩国人]
Why don't you try Korean?
等等
Oh, wait.
你"尝"过
You have.
鲁本  这没什么大不了的  好吗
Ruben, this is not a big deal. Okay?
你只要告诉索菲亚
You've just got to tell Sofia
你是我男朋友库珀的朋友
that you're a friend of my boyfriend, Cooper.
我跟这位库珀关系多好呢
How tight am I with this Cooper?
我们互相给对方起昵称了吗
I mean, do we have nicknames for each other?
这家伙会给我捐肾吗
Would the guy give me a kidney?
什么  你为什么需要肾
Why? Why do you need a kidney?
你的档案里没写啊
That was not in your profile.
听着  我觉得你的室友真的很可爱
Look, look, I think your roommate is really cute,
只不过我不太想撒谎
but I'm just not comfortable lying.
索菲亚
Sofia!
突然之间  我觉得无妨
And suddenly, I'm comfortable.
你真人比小库在公司给我...
You're even prettier than your piure...
看的照片更漂亮...
that Coop showed me at work
而且我不需要肾
where I don't need a kidney.
好吧  你也是技术男吧
O...kay. So you're in tech.
你是说科...技吗
Tech...nology?
他以前是  但现在不是了
He was, but now he's not.
对  我改行了
Yeah, I had a career change.
我在一家做三明治的公司上班
I work for an establishment that makes sandwiches.
叫做萨明治
It's called Sammich's.
你听说过吗
You heard of it?
快餐店嘛  听说过
Fast food, yes.
你有没有听说过有人得先走
Have you ever heard of someone having to leave a date early
因为她另有约呢
because she has an appointment?
-那人就是我  -索菲亚
- This is that. - Sofia.
我作为一名市场助理分管其中五家门店
I cover five of their franchises as a marketing associate.
我可以重新安排
I can reschedule.
当然
Yeah, you can.
库库跟我说你很聪明
You know, Coopster told me you were smart,
有趣  并且貌美如花
funny, and gorgeous.
要我说
If you ask me,
他所言非虚并且有过之无不及
he under-promised and over-delivered.
满嘴营销套话
Marketing speak.
加比  我刚想起来你另有约
Gabi, I just remembered that you have to leave early
你得先走
because you have an appointment.
-我没有啊  -你有
- No, I don't. - You do!
好吧
Okay.
早安  我最好的美女朋友
Good morning, my beautiful best friend.
在喝咖啡前说"早安"
Well, "good morning" before coffee?
看来某人的室友
It looks like somebody has a roommate
为她找到了真命天子
that found her the perfect guy!
小声点  他就在里面
Shh! He's in there right now.
不得了啊  妹子
Damn, girl.
弥补之前浪费的时光
Way to make up for lost time.
你的腿酸吗
Was it like riding a bicycle
还是像骑了环法车赛那么酸
or was it like riding a bicycle a whole bunch of times?
没有  我们就聊了聊天
No, all we did was talk.
光着身子吗
Naked?
没有  你知道我很保守的
No, you know I'm old fashioned.
至少得到第七次约会才能上床
Booty's gotta wait till at least the seventh date.
但他太优秀了  而且人又好又有志向
Ugh, but he is so amazing and sweet and ambitious.
另外  在他睡觉的时候我查了下他背景
Plus, I did a background check while he was sleeping.
没有前科
No priors.
没留尿样吗  你的要求放宽了
No urine sample? You're slipping.
总之  我要去洗澡了
Well, anyway, I'm gonna shower
因为他说他得去上班了
because he says he has to leave for work,
穿西装上班
where he wears a suit.
我终于和西装男约会了
I'm finally dating a guy who wears a suit!
加油加比  加油加比
Go Gabi, go Gabi.
鲁本
Hey, Ruben.
我以为你去上班了
I thought you left for work.
我没去
I did not.
该你说了
Your turn.
你是说穿着这一身吗
You mean this?
我穿这身是去上班的
I wear this for work.
索菲亚说你穿西装[套装]上班
Sofia said you wore a suit to work.
没错
I do.
火腿奶酪三明治套装
A ham and cheese sandwich suit.
什么
What?
什么情况
I mean, what?
穿成那样在萨明治店上班
You know, for Sammich's.
我就是萨明治店的吉祥物萨米
I'm Sammy the Sammich.
我的布偶服在车里
My costume's in the car.
天呐  我把索菲亚介绍给了一个三明治
Oh my God, I set Sofia up with a sandwich but--
等等  你说你是做市场营销的
Wait, you said you were in marketing.
人们看到我跳舞  然后来买三明治
Well, people see me dance, and they buy a sandwich--
市场营销
Marketing.
天呐
Oh my God.
这比用翻盖手机还差劲
This is so much worse than having a flip phone.
所以我不在初次约会的时候就说实情
That's why I don't tell girls on the first date.
她们会以工作取人
They can be a little judgy.
你是吉祥物好吗
Yeah, well, you are a Sammich.
要是索菲亚知道了  绝不会再跟你约会的
And if Sofia finds out, she is never gonna go out with you again.
我真的很喜欢她
I really like her.
我知道  我是她最好的朋友
I know, and I'm her best friend,
这个身份我想继续保持下去
and I want to continue to be,
所以你不能告诉她实情
so you just can't tell her.
好吗  向我保证
Okay? Promise me.
-好  -好  握手为誓
- Okay, yeah. - All right, shake on it!
天呐  我都做了什么
Oh God, what have I done?
天呐  我得删了这个应用
Oh, man. I've gotta delete this app.
给索菲亚介绍对象是我有过的最糟的主意
Setting up Sofia was the worst idea I've ever had.
你怎么知道呢
How would you know?
你都没有想出过一个好主意来进行比较
Don't you need to have a good idea to compare it to?
你知道吗  没关系的
You know what? It's fine.
一切都会好起来的
It'll be okay.
她会在他身上找到讨厌的地方
She'll find something about him that she hates,
然后她会在发现他是个三明治并跟我
and then she'll dump him before she finds out
绝交之前就甩了他的
he's a sandwich and dumps me.
加比
Ugh, Gabi!
别再发牢骚了
Enough with the incessant whining.
乔什
Josh!
我有麻烦了
I have a problem.
现在不是说这个的时候  艾略特
Now is not a good time, Elliot.
尤兰达在跟我以前的男朋友约会
Yolanda's dating someone I used to date.
-我该告诉她吗  -该
- Should I tell her? - Yes.
我还指望你另找门路...
I was hoping you'd go the other way...
就像马可以前那样
Like Marco used to.
听着  我也遇到了一点麻烦
Listen, I may have a little bit of a situation, too.
不管是什么麻烦
Whatever it is,
别在头脑发热的时候做出
don't do something in the heat of the moment
后悔终生的事
that you'll regret forever.
我只会这么做啊  你不认识我吗
That's all I do. Do you know me?
你还好吗
Are you okay?
还好  不  不好
I'm fine. No, I'm not.
我之前在想着有多替卡洛琳高兴
So I was thinking about how happy I am for Caroline,
所以我去了她家  送了她个结婚礼物
so I went over to her place and gave her a wedding gift.
真贴心  你送的什么
Oh, that's sweet. What'd you give her?
一次高潮
An orgasm.
什么
What?
我们上床了
We had sex.
是...
Y--
是  我知道高潮是什么
Yes, I know what an orgasm is!
只是不知道还能当礼物送人
I just didn't know that you could register for one.
天啊  我是怎么了
Oh my god, what is going on with me?
自从我跟卡洛琳分手  交往过了
I mean, since I broke up with Caroline, there's been
吉莉  劳伦  肖娜  差点有肖娜的女儿
Jilly, Lauren, Shauna, almost Shauna's daughter,
现在又回到了卡洛琳
and now back to Caroline.
你套了自己一圈呢
You lapped yourself.
我知道
I know.
高中的时候我肯定高兴坏了
High school Josh would have been stoked to be in this position,
但这不是我
but this is not me.
你猜怎么着
You know what?
在我想明白这事以前
I am not sleeping with any more women
不会再和女人睡觉了
until I figure out what is going on.
听着
Listen,
你不是最近唯一搞砸的人
you're not the only one who's been messing up recently.
我...
I, uh,
我不小心介绍了索菲亚一个三明治
I accidentally set Sofia up with a sandwich.
我看出你想干什么了  加比
I see what you're doing, Gabi.
你想编个比我干的还蠢的事
You're making up something more idiotic than what I did
好安慰我的心灵
to help me feel better about myself.
谢谢
Thank you.
是啊  我是在这样
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
尤兰达
Yolanda!
我有话跟你说
I have to tell you something!
在我吸尘的时候说吧
Tell me while I vacuum,
我赶着和马可约会呢
I have to hurry for my date with Marco!
就是这事
About that,
我以前和他约会过
I used to date him!
什么
What?
我以前和马可约会过
I used to date Marco!
你在说什么
What the hell you talkin' about?
马可喜欢女人
Marco likes women.
现在而已
Now.
我不相信你
I don't believe you.
有个鲨鱼纹身在他的两...
Shark tattoo right between the--
妈惹
Oh my damn!
对不起
I'm sorry.
马可一定是在探索性向
Marco must have been experimenting,
我就是他的实验室
and I was his laboratory.
不敢相信我会这么说
I can't believe I'm saying this,
但我不希望你受伤害
but I don't want you to get hurt.
因为就算马可变直了
'Cause even though Marco went straight,
可能还会弯回去
he still might fluctuate.
你真是贴心  艾略特
Oh, that is so sweet, Elliot.
不过我们现实点吧
But let's be real.
他游览过"亚洲风景"  但还是更爱我的风情
He went "Gaysian," then changed his persuasion.
我想了下和鲁本的事
I had a thought about Ruben.
你发现他吃东西很奇怪  然后甩了他是不是
Oh, you noticed he chews weird, and you kicked him to the curb?
他吃东西很完美
He chews perfectly.
终于遇到一个
Finally!
听着  重点是
Hey, listen, the point is
你状态又回来了
uh, you got your groove back.
所以现在可以重返情场
You know, so now you can get out there
和别人约会  而不是鲁本
and you can date other people, not Ruben.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
我终于遇到了个喜欢的男人
I finally meet a guy I like,
所以我要打破七次约会的规矩
that's why I'm breaking the seven-date rule
今晚就和他上床
on having sex tonight.
不  不要
No! No, no, no. Don't.
收起你的胯
Put that away!
规则很明确  好吗
The rule is very clear, okay?
真找不到缺点了再上床
Booty's gotta wait until you find things you hate.
好吧  怎么了
Okay, what is going on?
因为几天前
Because a couple of days ago,
你还等不急让我去约会
you couldn't wait for me to meet someone.
现在又想我甩了他吗
And now you want me to dump him?
好吧  坐下来
Okay, sit down.
鲁本有些事你会想知道的
There's something about Ruben you should know.
好吧  你说
Okay, well tell me.
因为我觉得他是完美的男人
Because I think he's the perfect man.
不是男人...
Not so much of a man...
是三明治人
as a manwich.
什么
What?
鲁本...
Ruben...
鲁本是种三明治的名字
是个三明治
is a sandwich.
是啊  加比
Yes, Gabi.
我猜他一定没听过这笑话
I'm sure he's never heard that one before.
不不不  我想说的是
No, no, no. No! Listen, my point is
鲁本是个三明治
Ruben is a sandwich,
一个职业三明治
a professional sandwich.
鲁本就是萨明治的萨米
Ruben is Sammy the sammich.
等等
Hold on.
你是说  那个站在外面...
You mean, the one that stands outside the--
-穿着...  -是
- With the-- - Yeah.
-还做着...  -是
- Who does the-- - Yeah.
-操他...  -走
- What the-- - Go!
我不懂了  你干嘛不像跟其他人一样
I don't understand. Why can't you just break up with him
发短信分手呢
over text like all the other ones?
因为他骗了我
Because he lied to me.
我差点就被他"治"了
I almost had a one-night "standwich."
他在这
Here he is.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
我们聊了一晚上
I mean, we stayed up all night talking.
说了那么多秘密
We shared intimate details of our lives.
我连你最喜欢的三明治都知道
I know your favorite sandwich!
你居然忘了说你自己也是
But you forgot to mention that you are one!
别推我
Don't push me!
不许推我闺蜜  过来
Nobody shoves my best friend. Come here!
你得道歉
You got to apologize!
你不是鲁本
You're not Ruben.
我当然不是
You're damn right I'm not.
五秒原则  对不起
Uh, five second rule. I'm so sorry!
真的对不起
I'm so sorry.
索菲亚  你来干什么
Sofia? What are you doing here?
天啊  那手套
Oh my god. The gloves.
你是个三明治
You are a sandwich!
我准备告诉你的
I was gonna tell you,
但加比逼我别告诉
but Gabi made me swear not to.
什么
What?
你居然想怪我
All right, you can't pin this all on me.
要不是你在婚介应用上
This never would have happened
填的假冒档案也不会这样
if you didn't lie to me on your HeyCupid profile.
等等  妹子
Back it up, sista.
档案
Profile?
我以为你说他是库珀的朋友
I thought you said he was a friend of Cooper's.
听着  我就直说了  好吧
Okay. Listen, I'm just gonna come clean. Okay?
库珀也用婚介应用...
Cooper went on HeyCupid--
-加比  -抱歉
- Gabi. - I'm sorry.
我假冒了你的交友档案
I set you up with a fake dating profile,
-因为我想帮你找到真命天子  -天啊
- 'cause I wanted you to find the perfect guy. - Oh my god.
这可过分了...
You know, this is too much...
即使对你来说
even for you.
这手套没中指算你走运
You're lucky this doesn't have a middle finger!
大家都在说这里
Everyone's talking about this place.
菜看起来也很好吃
And the food looks good.
上等腰肉牛排听着真棒
Oh, the porterhouse steak sounds awesome.
但中式鸡肉沙拉看起来也超好吃
Oh, but the Chinese chicken salad looks delish!
你两道菜都行[可直可弯]  是吗
So you can go either way, huh?
当然了
I sure can.
我觉得我要沙拉吧
I think I'll have the salad.
我喜欢亚洲酱料[穿衣服]
I love an Asian dressing.
或者不穿
And undressing.
我们快点餐吧
Let's hurry and order.
早点吃完
The sooner we eat,
就能早点燃烧掉这些卡路里
the sooner we can burn off these calories.
想得美  艾略特
Oh, hell no, Elliot!
艾略特
Elliot?
我看出来了
I see what this is about.
他告诉了你我们以前约会过
He told you we used to date
我和男人在一起过吓到你了
and it freaks you out that I've been with men.
不  不
Oh, no, no.
我无所谓  随你喜欢男女
I'm cool with that. Whatever floats your boat.
但喜欢艾略特...
But Elliot?
过去的事就别再说了吧
Let's leave the past in the past.
今晚只有我们两个
Tonight is just you and me.
没错
Oh, you're right.
是我在犯傻
I'm being silly.
不行
I can't.
对不起  艾略特  我是说马可...
I'm sorry, Elliot-- I mean, Marco--
艾马特  再见
El Marco. Bye!
我一直在想着和卡洛琳那事
This whole Caroline thing just really screwed with my head.
我得锻炼一下分分心
I need to work out some frustration.
你就不能借酒浇愁吗  像我爸那样
Couldn't you just drink, like my dad?
真是愚蠢
I mean, it was so stupid.
我都对她没感觉了
I don't even have feelings for her anymore.
什么也不算啊
It meant nothing.
好疼
Ouch!
我知道  听着很残忍  但这是事实
Yeah, I know. It sounds harsh, but it's true.
我们俩根本不配  那些姑娘都不配
She was never right for me. None of these girls were.
我干嘛还要和她们勾搭呢
Why do I keep hooking up with all these women?
好吧  你得停下
Okay, you need to stop.
我也想啊  艾略特  我也想
I wish I could, Elliot. I wish I could.
好疼的
It hurts!
你说得没错  是疼
You're damn right, it does,
但或许我胡搞就是为了掩盖心痛
but maybe I bury this pain by sleeping around.
你为什么要这样
Why are you doing this?
或许因为我想  艾略特
Maybe because I want that feeling, Elliot.
想要那种为某人痴狂的感觉
The feeling you get when you're excited about somebody,
相处多久都不满足
when you can't get enough of them.
你只能想着她们...
All you do is think about them...
就像我对加比的感觉
the way I feel about Gabi.
加比吗
Gabi?
天啊  就是这个
Oh my god, that's it.
我还对加比有感觉
I still have feelings for Gabi.
现在怎么办
Now what?
喊救护车
Call 911.
就算我吃着这个你做的
Even though I am eating this sundae you made
想挽回我友谊的圣代
to buy back my friendship,
也不代表我就原谅你了
It does not mean that I have forgiven you.
索菲亚  我发现你在把杏仁
Sofia, I noticed that you are picking out
拣到一边  不吃它们
and not eating the almonds.
你别说了
Let me stop you right there.
我懂你的小把戏
I know what you're doing.
你在我圣代里放杏仁
You put almonds in my sundae,
明知道我不喜欢
knowing that I do not like them,
因为就算圣代不完美
because even though the sundae's not perfect,
我还是很喜欢吃
I'll love it anyway.
你懂我的寓意了吗
Oh, did you pick up on that?
这是行不通的  因为圣代不是人
And it's not gonna work because a sundae isn't a person,
除非你又想介绍个
unless you're planning to set me up
穿成圣代的人给我
with a person who dresses like a sundae.
我来问你  谁是你人生中
Let me ask you something. Who's the biggest disaster
-遇见最烂的人  -你
- you've ever met in your whole life? - You.
好吧  首先  你回答的太快了
Okay, first off, you answered that too fast.
其次
And second,
忽略今天发生的事情
despite what happened today,
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
当然了
Of course I do.
那为什么你可以接受我的所有缺点
Well, then why is it you can accept all of my flaws
依然爱我  但却不能对和你
and still love me, but you can't do that
约会的男生也这样呢
with the guys that you date?
我不知道
I don't know.
跟男生怎么一样呢
It's just different with guys.
是吗
Oh, is it?
是啊  他们...
Yes, I mean, they're...
他们像...
They're like...
他们...
They do--
你说的在理
Wow, that's a really good point.
那我再问你
Well, let me ask you another question.
如果我是三明治你还爱我吗
Would you still love me if I was a sandwich?
天啊
Oh my god.
我的计划有用了
My plan has worked.
鲁本
Ruben!
真的很抱歉
I am so, so sorry!
我真的喜欢你
I really like you,
我不在乎你是不是三明治
and I don't care if you're a sandwich.
只要瞒着我爸妈就好
We just won't tell my parents.
请告诉我我没找错人
Oh, please tell me I have the right one.
没有
Yeah, you do.
谢天谢地
Thank god!
马可  我就感觉你会打来
Marco, I had a feeling you'd call.
我只是想为麦当娜演唱会那事道歉
I just wanted to make up for the Madonna concert.
我不是想炫耀  但我名草有主了
Papa don't mean to preach, but I have a boyfriend.
我只是觉得既然你来了
I just thought that since you're here,
说明你和你男友也没那么坚贞嘛
you and your boyfriend aren't exclusive.
我们只是喝杯酒
It's just a drink.
是啊  我们见面那晚你也是这么说的
Yeah, that's what you said the night we met.
看着我的眼睛
Look me in the eye
告诉我你对我没有性趣  宝贝
and tell me that you're not attracted to me, baby.
告诉我你不想和我在一起
That you don't want a big slice of this.
抱歉  我做不到
Sorry, I can't do this!
马可...尤兰达...马兰达
Marco-- Yolanda-- Malanda.
再见
Bye!